Neil V. Rosenberg bluegrass music collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Sound recordings, Digital files are located in afc2002009_dc001. Please see the AFC reference staff for access.
  - Dubs of radio shows from home discs, AFC 2002/009: SR163; RXI 0163; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:31:08, Side 2: 00:31:03): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - "How Beautiful Heaven Must Be" - Uncle Dave Macon and Dorris Macon
      - "If I Should Wander Back Tonight"
      - "My Rose Of Old Kentucky"
      - "My Little Honeysuckle Rose"
      - "Summertime Is Past And Gone"
      - "Heavy Traffic Ahead"
      - "I'm Travellin' On And On"
      - "Cumberland Gap"
      - "Black Jack Davy"
      - "Everyone Knew It But Me"
      - "That Home Above"
      - "Bluegrass Special"
      - "I Don't Love Nobody"
      - "Goodbye Old Pal"
    - Side 2
      - "The Shining Path"
      - "Summertime Is Past And Gone"
      - "Nine Pound Hammer"
      - "From Jerusalem To Jericho" - Uncle Dave Macon and Dorris Macon
      - "You're Drifting Away" - Uncle Dave Macon and Dorris Macon
      - "Old Joe Clark"
      - * "Shine Hallelujah Shine"
      - * "How Will I Explain About You"
      - * "Little Community Church"
      - * "Muleskinner Blues"
      - "Little Cabin Home On The Hill"
      - "When You're Blue Just Yodel" - Irene and Lou with the Blue Grass Boys
      - "Little Community Church"
      - "Mule Skinner Blues #2
  - Dubs of radio shows from home discs, 1946-1948, AFC 2002/009: SR164; RXI 0164; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:31:08, Side 2: 00:32:06): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    Radio station WSW, Nashville, Tennessee. Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys (unless otherwise noted). Personnel: Bill Monroe, mandolin; Lester Flatt, guitar; Earl Scruggs, banjo; Chubby Wise, fiddle; Howard Watts (Cedric Rainwater), bass.
    - Side 1
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys
        - "How Will I Explain About You"
        - "Blue Moon Of Kentucky"
        - Rod Brasfield intro - Red Foley
        - "Goodbye Old Pal"
        - "We'll Meet Again Sweetheart"
        - "There Ain't Nobody Gonna Miss Me"
      - Uncle Dave Macon and Dorris Macon
        - "Going Down Town"
        - "Dear Old Dixie"
          On the accompanying song list, a line is drawn between this title and the preceding title.
        - "John Henry"
        - "Whitehouse Blues"
        - "Little Cabin Home On The Hill"
        - "Remember The Cross"
        - "Molly And Tenbrooks"
        - "Sweetheart You Done Me Wrong"
        - "Remember The Cross"
    - Side 2
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys
        - "Molly And Tenbrooks"
      - ad for Wallright
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys
        - "Mule Skinner Blues"
        - "John Henry"
          As on Bluegrass Anthology 05
        - "Love Gone Cold"
      - "Brown's Ferry Blues"
        Jackie Phelps (guitar) with the Blue Grass Boys
      - "Tennessee Gambler"
        Mel and Stan Hankinson with the Blue Grass Boys
      - "Just A Message"
        Melissa Monroe with the Blue Grass Boys
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys
        - "Rocky Road Blues"
        - "I'm Travelin' On And On"
      - Selections from the same show
        - songbook ad
        - "Dear Old Dixie"
          The source disc was cracked
        - "My Little Honeysuckle Rose"
        - fruit tree ad: K-F ad
        - "Mule Skinner Blues"
        - theme and ending
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys
        - "Cumberland Gap"
        - "My Little Honeysuckle Rose"
        - "Orange Blossom Special"
        - "Blue Yodel No. 4"
  - Stanley Brothers at Bean Blossom, October 16, 1966, AFC 2002/009: SR165; RXI 0201; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:48:22, Side 2: 00:32:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    Recorded at the evening show, Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. According to Neil Rosenberg, this was Carter Stanley's last show. Personnel: Ralph Stanley, banjo; Carter Stanley, guitar; George Shuffler, guitar; "Big Wilbur" Miller, bass.
    - Side 1
      - Dixie (Mason-Dixon Line) "My Dixie Home"
      - "I Know What It Means To Be Lonesome"
      - "I See Through You"
      - "Somebody Loves You Darling"
      - "Wildwood Flower"
      - "A Soldier's Grave"
      - "Rosewood Casket"
      - "If I Lose Let Me Lose"
      - "Charming Betsy"
      - "Down Yonder"
      - "Lost Train Blues"
      - Introduction to "Canaan's Land"
    - Side 2
      - Canaan's Land
      - "A Beautiful Life"
      - Intermission
      - "Little Maggie"
      - "Single Girl, Married Girl"
      - Medley
        - "Worried Man Blues"
        - "Roll In My Sweet Baby's Arms"
        - "Long Journey Home"
      - "Dang Me"
      - "Shouting On The Hills Of Glory"
      - "Pray For The Boys"
      - "She'll Be Coming 'Round The Mountain"
  - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at Bean Blossom, October 30, 1966, AFC 2002/009: SR166; RXI 0202; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:44:36, Side 2: 00:38:39): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    Recorded at the afternoon show, Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Personnel: Pete Rowan, guitar; Lamar Grier, banjo; Richard Greene, fiddle; Jim Monroe, bass. Continued on SR167.
    - Side 1
      - Intro: Birch "my brother and your friend"
      - "Watermelon"
      - "500 times" again
      - "Panhandle Country"
      - "Sunny Side Of The Mountain"
      - "Walls Of Time"
      - "Bluegrass Breakdown"
      - "Molly And Tenbrooks"
      - "You'll Find Her Name Written There"
      - "Brand New Shoes"
        Richard's solo; encore
      - "Blue Moon Of Kentucky"
      - "Roanoke"
      - "Toy Heart"
      - "Bluegrass Special"
        Jim and Pete take breaks too
      - "California Blues"
      - "Uncle Pen" - speech
      - "A Beautiful Life"
    - Side 2
      - "Shine On Me"
      - Birch and Bill talk - Tex Logan
      - "Christmas Time's A'Coming"
      - intermission
      - "Durang's Hornpipe"
      - "Coming Down From Boston"
      - Bill Dudley stealing wives and Virginia - speech
      - "Just A Little Talk With Jesus"
      - "Lost Indian"
      - "Shenandoah Valley Breakdown"
      - "Old Old House"
      - "I Live In The Past"
      - "Little Girl And The Dreadful Snake"
      - "Devil's Dream"
      - "Orange Blossom Special"
      - "Footprints In The Snow"/"John Henry"
      - "Y'all Come"
  - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at Bean Blossom, October 30, 1966, AFC 2002/009: SR167; RXI 0203; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:37:53, Side 2: 00:48:17): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    Recorded at the evening show, Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Personnel: Pete Rowan, guitar; Richard Greene, fiddle; Lamar Grier, banjo; Jim Monroe, bass. Continued from SR166.
    - Side 1
      - "Shady Grove"
      - "I'm Knocking On Your Door"
      - "True Life Blues"
      - "Crossing The Cumberland"
      - "You Won't Be Satisfied That Way"
      - "Muleskinner Blues"
      - "Dusty Miller"
      - "Blue Ridge Mountain Blues"
      - "Twinkle Little Star"
      - "Pike County Breakdown"
      - "Four Walls"
      - "Mary At The Home Place"
      - "First Whippoorwill"
      - "Blue Grass Stomp"
      - "Cotton Fields"
      - "Orange Blossom Special"
      - "Little Rabbit"
    - Side 2
      - "Little Rabbit"
      - "Life's Railway To Heaven"
      - "Wayfaring Stranger"
      - "In The Pines"
      - intermission
      - "Panhandle Country"
      - "When My Blue Moon Turns To Gold Again"
      - "Florida Blues"
      - "Boating Up Sandy"
      - "Boat Of Love"
      - "Careless Love"
        Speech about spring
      - "Uncle Pen"
        More speech
      - "Rawhide"
        Speeches by band members
      - "Y'all Come"
  - Mainer's Mountaineers singles, July 1966, AFC 2002/009: SR168; John Morris collection (via Chuck Crawford); 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side 1: 00:59:17, Side 2: 00:58:56): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    The group recorded under various versions of this name. Dubs of commercial recordings, made in July 1966.
    - Side 1
      - "How Can I Be Your Sweetheart," undated
      - "Now I Must Travel Alone," undated
      - "Ship Sailing Now," 1935
        Bb-6088 [BS94328]
      - "This World Is Not My Home," 1935
        Bb-6088 [BS94329]
      - "Just One Way To The Pearly Gates," 1937
        Bb-6784 (BS02533]
      - "I'll Be A Friend Of Jesus," 1937
        Bb-6784 (BS02536]
      - "Sparkling Blue Eyes," 1939
        Bb-8249 [BS041200]
      - "The Gospel Cannon Ball," 1939
        Bb-8249 [BS041203]
      - "Are You Still Lonesome Too," undated
        This may be "Happy Or Lonesome"
      - "Since I Met My Mother-In-Law," 1938
        Bb-7742 [BS018766]
      - "One Little Word," undated
      - "Wabash Cannonball," undated
      - "What Would You Give In Exchange," 1936
        Bb-8073 [BS99135]
      - "Sleep On," 1936
        Montgomery Ward [label], with Ruth West
      - "The Same Old You To Me," 1938
        Bb-7924 [BS026987]
      - "A Little Love," 1938
        Bb-7924 [BS027700]
      - "Kiss Me Cindy," 1937
        Bb-7289 [BS011998]
      - "Don't Get Trouble In Your Mind," 1937
        Bb-7289 [BS011997]
      - "Maple On The Hill," 1935
        Bb-6065 [BS94330]
      - "Take Me In The Lifeboat," 1935
        Bb-6065 [BS94331]
      - "Take Me Home To The Sweet Sunny South," 1936
        Bb-6479 [BS102603]
      - "The Old And Faded Picture," 1936
        Bb-6479 [BS102602]
    - Side 2
      - "I'm Living The Right Life Now," 1938
        Bb-7412 [BS018605]
      - "When It's Lamp-Lighting Time In Heaven," 1938
        Bb-7412 [BS018606]
      - "Kiss Me Cindy," 1937
      - "Don't Get Trouble In Your Mind," 1937
      - "Little Birdie," 1937
        Bb-6840 [Bb07051]
      - "Starting Life Anew With You," 1937
        Bb-6840 [Bb07053]
      - "Shake Hands With Mother," 1936
        Bb-6596 [BS102617]
      - "Walk That Lonesome Valley," 1936
        Bb-6596 [BS102604]
      - "Lights In The Valley," 1935
        Bb-6160 [BS94342]
      - "The City On The Hill," 1935
        Bb-6160 [BS94339]
      - "Garden Of Prayer," 1937
        Bb-7362 [BS011824]
      - "Jesus Paid The Debt For Me," undated
      - "Train Carry My Girl Back Home," 1937
        Bb-6890 [BS07055]
      - "Always Been A Rambler," 1937
        Bb-6890 [BS07052]
      - "Nobody's Darling On Earth, 1936
        Bb-6460 [Bb102616]
      - "If I Could Hear My Mother," 1936
        Bb-6460 [Bb102615]
      - "That Picture On The Wall"
      - "Came Down From The Skies"
      - "Goin' To Georgia," 1936
        Bb-6423 [BS99139]
      - "Maple On The Hill," 1935
  - Kentucky Colonels, 1965, AFC 2002/009: SR169; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; 00:32:50): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
    Speed-corrected redub of SR115
    - Side 1
      - "Orange Blossom Special"
      - "Uncle Pen"
      - "Footprints In The Snow"
      - "Let Me Fall"
      - "Eighth Of January"
    - Side 2
      - "Hot Corn, Cold Corn"
      - "Shuckin' Of The Corn"
      - "Dark Hollow"
      - "May You Never Be Alone"
      - "Soldier's Joy"
      - "Train 45"
        Identified as "Reuben" in the documentation for SR115.
  - Kentucky Colonels, 1965, AFC 2002/009: SR170; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; 00:30:29): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
    Speed-corrected redub of part of SR114
    - "Fire On The Mountain"
    - "Don't Let Your Deal Go Down"
    - "John Hardy"
    - "For Lovin' Me"
      Identified as "That's What You Get For Lovin' Me" in the documentation for SR114.
    - "Alabama Jubilee"
    - "New River Train"
    - "Running Gun"
    - "Ocean Of Diamonds"
    - "Bluegrass Breakdown"
    - "Hard-Hearted"
      Identified as "Hardhearted Heart Breaker" in the documentation for SR114.
    - "Wicked Path Of Sin"
    - "Get Down On Your Knees And Pray"
  - Kentucky Colonels, 1965, AFC 2002/009: SR171; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; 00:32:31): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
    Speed-corrected redub of part of SR114.
    - "Orange Blossom Special"
    - "Train 45"
    - "I'm Gonna Do Away With Me"
      Identified as "If You're Ever Gonna Leave Me" in the documentation for SR114.
    - "Kicking Mule"
      Identified as "Johnson's Old Grey Mule" in the documentation for SR114.
    - "I'm Just A Used-To-Be To You"
    - "Black Mountain Rag"
    - "Crawdad Song"
    - "Julius Finkbein's Rag"
    - "Once A Day"
    - "Rawhide"
    - "Over In The Glory Land"
      Identified as "Over In Glory Land" in the documentation for SR114.
    - "Cacklin' Hen"
  - Radio dubs of Mac Wiseman and the Country Boys, circa 1954-1955, AFC 2002/009: SR172; Marvin Hedrick; RXI 0165; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:32:08, Side 2: 00:32:10): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    Allen Shelton, banjo. Continued on SR173.
    - Side 1
      - "Lonesome Road Blues"
      - "When I Get The Money Made"
      - "A Strand From A Yellow Curl"
      - "I'm Walking The Dog"
      - "When God Dips His Love In My Heart"
      - "Bonapart's Retreat"
      - "Home Sweet Home"
      - "Engine Number Three"
      - "When The Snow Flakes Fall Again"
      - "If I Could Kiss Your Sweet Lips Tonight"
      - "From The Manger To The Cross"
      - "Love Letters In The Sand"
      - "Patty On The Turnpike"
      - "Remembering"
      - "Marriage Is Alright"
      - "Sunny Mountain Chimes"
    - Side 2
      - "Sunny Mountain Chimes"
      - "When It's Reveille Time In Heaven"
      - "The Waltz You Saved For Me"
      - "Keep On The Sunny Side"
      - "It's Been So Long"
        Not Wiseman
      - "Let Me Borrow Your Heart"
      - "Don't Let Your Sweet Love Die"
      - "Waiting For The Boys"
      - "Fire In My Heart"
      - "I'll Still Write Your Name In The Sand"
      - "I'm Going To See My Baby"
      - "I'd Rather Live By The Side Of The Road"
      - "You're Sweeter Than The Honey"
  - Radio dubs of Mac Wiseman and the Country Boys; Don Reno and Red Smiley and the Tennessee Cutups, circa 1954-1955, AFC 2002/009: SR173; Marvin Hedrick; RXI 0166; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:33:17, Side 2: 00:08:41): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    Continued from SR172.
    - Side 1
      - Mac Wiseman and the Country Boys
        - "Shackles And Chains"
        - "The Talk Of The Town"
        - "Live And Let Live"
        - "Hide Away"
        - "Pike County Breakdown"
        - "You're Going Like Wildfire"
        - "I'm A Stranger Here"
        - "Homestead On The Farm"
        - "It's So Long And Goodbye To You"
        - "Six More Miles"
        - "Crazy Blues"
        - "You'd Better Wake Up"
        - "Long Journey Home"
        - "Georgia Waltz"
        - "Cumberland Gap"
    - Side 2
      - Mac Wiseman and the Country Boys
        - "Cumberland Gap"
        - "Are You Coming Back To Me"
        - "I Heard My Mother Call My Name In Prayer"
      - Don Reno and Red Smiley and the Tennessee Cutups
        - "Jesus Is Standing At My Right Hand"
  - Charlie Bailey singles with Osbornes, AFC 2002/009: SR174; Bobby Osborne; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; 00:17:59): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Louvin Brothers
      - "Weapon Of Prayer"
    - Sonny Osborne
      - "Mule Skinner Blues"
        Kentucky
    - Charlie Bailey, guitar; Bob Osborne, mandolin; Sonny Osborne, banjo; Clarence "Tater" Tate, fiddle; probably E.P. "Jake" Tullock, bassist
      Selections from Country Hymns CH-17. Tullock's name and "Tater" Tate's first name were not identified in the documentation; these are the archivist's additions.
      - "Standing Somewhere In The Shadows I'll Find Jesus"
      - "I'm Going To Serve Him 'Till I Die"
      - "When He Reached Down For Me"
    - Charlie Bailey, guitar; Bob Osborne, mandolin; Sonny Osborne, banjo; Clarence "Tater" Tate, fiddle; probably E.P. "Jake" Tullock, bassist
      Selections from Country Hymns CH-16. Tullock's name and "Tater" Tate's first name were not identified in the documentation; these are the archivist's additions.
      - "A Tramp On The Street"
      - "Ashamed To Own The Blessed Savior"
      - "Where The Soul Of Man Never Dies"
  - Osborne Brothers at The Outpost Bar, March 17, 1967, AFC 2002/009: SR175; RXI 0167; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:31:41, Side 2: 00:32:09): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    Recorded at The Outpost Bar, Sullivan Street, on the West Side, Columbus Ohio; first set. Continued on SR176.
    - Side 1
      - "Salty Dog Blues"
      - "I'll Be Alright Tomorrow"
      - "Me And My Old Banjo"
      - "Blue Moon Of Kentucky"
      - "Making Plans"
      - "Bugle Call Rag"
        "New rhythmic thing"
      - "Cotton Fields"
      - "Yesterday's Gone"
      - "Up This Hill And Down"
        "Sonny's new banjo lick"
      - "The Kind Of Woman I Got"
      - "Ruby"
        Sonny breaks the fifth string
    - Side 2
      - "Take This Hammer"
      - "Pathway Of Teardrops"
      - "Lonesome Day"
      - "May You Never Be Alone"
      - "Cripple Creek"
      - "Fair And Tender Ladies"
      - "Memories" ("J-E-L-L-O")
      - "Kentucky"
      - "Hard Times"
      - "Foggy Mountain Breakdown"
      - "I Saw Your Face In The Moon"
      - "Girl In The Blue Velvet Band"
  - Osborne Brothers at Emerson Supper Club, and at The Outpost Bar; Alex Campbell, Ola Belle Reed, and the New River Boys, AFC 2002/009: SR176; RXI 0168; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:32:04, Side 2: 00:20:33): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - Osborne Brothers at Emerson Supper Club, April 6, 1967
        Recorded at Emerson Supper Club, Beach Grove; Emerson, Indianapolis, Indiana.
        - "Big Spike Hammer"
        - "Take This Hammer"
        - "Kentucky"
        - "Cotton Fields"
        - "Foggy Mountain Breakdown"
        - "Making Plans"
        - unidentified song
          Harley Gabbard, dobro
        - "Understand Your Man"
        - "Wreck Of The Old 97"
        - "Fair And Tender Ladies"
    - Side 2
      - Osborne Brothers at The Outpost Bar, March 17, 1967
        Continued from SR175.
        - "Making Plans"
        - unidentified tune
          Wade Ray instrumental
        - "My Aching Heart"
        - "Lonesome Road Blues"
      - Osborne Brothers at Emerson Supper Club, April 6, 1967
        - "Roll Muddy River"
      - Alex Campbell, Ola Belle Reed, and the New River Boys, circa 1965
        Dub of the LP Old Time Singing With String Band (Ken-Del 4950). Alex and Ola Belle were brother and sister. Continued from SR179.
        - "Bring'in In The Georgia Mail"
        - "John Henry"
        - "Roll-On, Buddy, Roll-On"
        - "Whitehouse Blues"
          Carter Family lyrics
        - "Wildwood Flower"
  - The Greenhorns, December 24-25, 1966, AFC 2002/009: SR177; Yukio Mizuno; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side 1: 00:14:26, Side 2: 00:15:31): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 5 in.
    Japanese bluegrass band. Personnel: Keisuke Sato, guitar and lead vocal; Takashi Okuhara, mandolin and harmonica; Yukio Mizuno, banjo, guitar, and autoharp; Kazuhiro Koshi, bass and guitar.
    - Side 1
      - "Raise A Ruckus"
        Additional personnel: Takayoshi Ishizaki, fiddle
      - "A Few More Years"
      - "Rabbit In The Log"
        Additional personnel: T. Okuhara and Y. Mizuno sing the same tenor harmony
      - "A Minor Breakdown"
      - "I Wonder How The Old Folks Are At Home"
        Additional personnel: Takayoshi Ishizaki, fiddle; Y. Mizuno sings tenor harmony
      - "We Shall Not Be Moved"
    - Side 2
      - "Down Yonder"
      - "Are You Washed In The Blood"
      - "Will The Circle Be Unbroken"
        Additional personnel: T. Okuhara sings vocal solo and plays harmonica
      - "Cannon Ball Blues"
        Additional personnel: Y. Mizuno, guitar
      - "Harbor Of Love"
      - "Foggy Mountain Special"
        Additional personnel: Takayoshi Ishizaki, fiddle; K. Koshi, guitar
  - Bluegrass Blackjacks at Bean Blossom; Ann Arbor Band at Bean Blossom; Dubs of 45 rpm discs, AFC 2002/009: SR178; RXI 0204; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:32:34, Side 2: 00:26:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Side 1
      - Bluegrass Blackjacks at Bean Blossom, April 2, 1967
        - "Ain't Nobody Gonna Miss Me When I'm Gone"
        - "500 Miles"
        - "Turkey In The Straw"
        - "These Men Of God"
        - "It's A Long Long Way To The Top Of The World"
      - Ann Arbor Band at Bean Blossom, April 2, 1967
        Recorded at the Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Personnel: Doug Green, guitar; "Snake," fiddle; unidentified musician, banjo.
        - "Kentucky Chimes"
        - "Little Cabin Home On The Hill"
        - "Devil's Dream"
        - "May The Circle Be Unbroken"
        - "Pretty Little Indian"
        - "Sitting Along In The Moonlight"
        - "Grey Eagle"
    - Side 2
      - Dubs of 45 rpm discs
        - "God Is Always The Same" - Jimmy Martin, 1962
          Decca 31376 (108637)
        - "Landslide Special" - McCormick Brothers, 1964
          Hickory 45-1245 (45-F-396)
        - "Wedding Band" - Jim Greer and Mac-O-Chee Valley Folks, 1962
          Nashville NV-5084
        - "Pretty Country Girl" - Jim Greer and Mac-O-Chee Valley Folks, 1962
        - "The Banjo And The Butterfly" - Mike Miller and Jack Casey and the Stone Mountain Boys, 1961
          Starday SEP 167
        - "Yesterday Was Only A Dream" - Mike Miller and Jack Casey and the Stone Mountain Boys, 1961
        - "You've Broken Her Heart" - Mike Miller and Jack Casey and the Stone Mountain Boys, 1961
        - "A Memory Of You" - Mike Miller and Jack Casey and the Stone Mountain Boys, 1961
        - "I'm Lost Between The Falling Snow" - Luke Thompson and His Green River Boys, 1961
          Hammond 4461
        - "Mountain Sweetheart" - Luke Thompson and His Green River Boys, 1961
        - "The Flame Of Love" - Jim and Jesse and the Virginia Boys, 1961
          Columbia 4-41938
  - Alex Campbell, Ola Belle Reed, and the New River Boys; Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at Bean Blossom, AFC 2002/009: SR179; RXI 0205; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 00:32:49, Side 2: 00:32:06): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
    - Tape Side 1
      - Alex Campbell, Ola Belle Reed, and the New River Boys, circa 1965
        Dub of the LP Old Time Singing With String Band (Ken-Del 4950). Alex and Ola Belle were brother and sister. Continued on SR176.
        - LP Side 1
          - "Little Darl'in" [sic]
          - "You've Always Wanted"
          - "Me And My Fiddle"
          - "Cumberland Gap"
          - "Come And Knock"
          - "Send Me The Pillow"
          - "New River Train"
          - "The Grey Eagle Hornpipe"
          - "Don't Ya Call My Name"
          - "Sweet Fern"
        - LP Side 2
          - "Will You Miss Me"
          - "Do You Wonder"
          - "Little Garden"
          - "Sourwood Mountain"
          - "Before I Met You"
          - "Walking With You In My Dreams"
    - Tape Side 2
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at Bean Blossom, April 2, 1967
        Recorded at the last half of the afternoon show, Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Personnel: Lamar Grier, banjo; Miles (Mylos) Sonka, guitar; Byron Berline, fiddle; James Monroe, bass.
        - "Roanoke"
        - "Pretty Fair Maiden"
        - "Grey Eagle"
        - "A Beautiful Life"
        - "Y'all Come"
      - Bill Monroe and His Blue Grass Boys at Bean Blossom, April 2, 1967
        Recorded at the evening show, Brown County Jamboree, Bean Blossom, Indiana. Continued on SR180.
        - "Monroe's Hornpipe"
        - "Dark Hollow"
        - "Little Cabin Home"
        - "Bugle Call Rag"
        - "Little Girl And The Dreadful Snake"
        - "Cheyenne"